I just talked about one of the things
that really works in my life the second
thing that really works in my life is
cohousing dinners I've been involved in
this co-hosting project since it first
started in Vancouver and I was not able
to financially move in with other people
who bought and are renting there but I
have been welcomed and accepted to be
part of the community dinners so four
times a week
the adults cook and clean there's about
a three to four week cycle so every
adult takes a turn cooking and cleaning
turn on time period and the kids are
getting more involved - acquired - it's
more for fun and learning and the amount
of community it's added the ability to
eat good nutritious food at a lower cost
and more diversity than I would
definitely able to offer my child to not
have to make a meal myself and then have
my child rejected have a reject someone
else's food it feels it feels better
somehow and yeah it's just an amazing
space and just so finding a way to
recreate that for people that don't live
in cohousing I realize the space that
they're in is created around that so
they have a community kitchen that seats
I don't know like 40 to 50 people and a
kitchen to cook in together that isn't
one of their kitchens but I think you
can recreate it in smaller ways with
five neighbors or five households where
each of you are cooking a different
night of the week or maybe it's just fun
days and every you know Monday with four
other families just being able to offer
that other that community space not
having to buy food on our own cooking
together eating together is such a
blessing in my life and loves you able
to recreate that on a larger scale
larger smaller scale so smaller people
with smaller groups of people but more
opportunity for everyone
that is Apple number 36